Washingtoniana Vertical File Index VF.001 VF.001
Test
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Q - R - S
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Q
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Quota Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ra - Ri
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ra - Rz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. RADA (Research Analysis Development Action, Inc.)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Radio Control Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Rape Crisis Center SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations. D.C. Rape Crisis Center
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Reading is Fundamental
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ready, Willing and Able
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Reciprocity Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Red Circle
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Refrigeration Trade Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Religious Heritage of America, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Restaurant Association of Metropolitan Washington, Inc. (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Rf - Rz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Robert T. Freeman Dental Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Rotary (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Round-up of Directors of Information Services (RUDIS)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Rowac Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Rubinstein Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sa - Si
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sa - Sz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Safeway Association (SEA)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Saint Andrew's Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Saint Columba's Scottish Country Dance Group
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Saint Luke's Society of Catholic Physicians
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Saint Peter Claver Center
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Saint Vincent de Paul Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Science Clubs
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Scribblers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sea Scouts
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Second Genesis
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Security Traders Association of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Senior Citizens Clubs
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sentinel Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Seymour Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Shriners (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Si -
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sierra Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ski Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Smithsonian Associates
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Soc - Sz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Social Hygiene Society of D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society for Creative Anachronism
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society for Philosophical Inquiry of Washington, D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society for the Advancement of Management. Washington Chapter
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society for the Preservation and Encouragement of Barber Shop Quartet Singing in America, Inc. (SPEBSQSA)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Colonial Wars in D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of F - Society of Z
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Mayflower Descendants of the District
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Military Widows
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Natives
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Professional Salesmen
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of the Cincinnati (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of the War of 1812 in the District of Columbia
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Washington Artists
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Washington Printmakers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Society of Woman Geographers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sociologists Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sod - Sz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Soldiers, Sailors, Marines and Airmen's Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sons of the American Revolution
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Soroptimist Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. South Washington Improvement Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Southeast Hillcrest Recreation Center Preschool Parents Center
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Southeast Ministers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Southeast Women's Christian Union
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Southern Christian Leadership Conference (SCLC)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Southern Society of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Special Libraries Association (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. State Societies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. State Societies. Pamphlets
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Stewards and Caterers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee (SNCC)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sulgrave Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sunshine and Community Society of the District of Columbia
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Support Center of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sycamore Island Club, Montgomery County, MD
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ta - Th
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ta - Tz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Tail-Waggers Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Takoma Horticultural Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Takoma Park Women's Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Tantalus Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Telephone Pioneers of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Thalian Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Theosophical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Thornton Society of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Thrifty Savers Buying Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Thumbs Up
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Thursday Network
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ti - Tz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Topside Aviation Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Torch Club of Washington, D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Tots and Teens
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Touchdown Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Traffic Club of Washington, D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. TransAfrica
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Travel Clubs
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Travelers Aid Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Tuesday Evening Club of Social Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Turtle Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Twentieth Century Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. U
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. UCLA Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Union and Literary Debating Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Union Soldiers Alliance of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Daughters of the Confederacy, D.C. Division
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Jewish Appeal of Greater Greater Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Nations Association of America, D.C. Chapter
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Nations Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Nations Service Center
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Planning Organization
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Service Organization (USO) SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YMCA. Historical Record of Washington YMCA - USO Club.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United Spanish War Veterans
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United States Capitol Historical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. United World Federalists, Washington Chapter
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Unity Support Group
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. University Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. University Legal Services
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. University - Neighborhoods Council (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. University Women's Club, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Urban Coalition SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Metropolitan Urban Coalition
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Urban Institute
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Urban Studies Libraries
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. V
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Va - Vz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Variety Club of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Vegetarian Society of D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Veterans of Foreign Wars, D.C. Department
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Victorian Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Vietnam Moratorium Committee
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Visiting Nurse Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Vocational Guidance Bureau of Washington, D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Voice
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Volunteers of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wa - Wz (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Walsh - Washington C
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wanderbirds
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. War Resisters League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ward 2 Tenants Council
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Action Group
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Animal Rescue League SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Animal Rescue League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Area Bicyclist Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Area Lawyers for the Arts
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Area Research Round Table
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Astrological Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Baltimore Regional Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Bar Association of D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Benevolent Filmmakers League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Biologists Field Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Board of Rabbis
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Board of Realtors SEE Real Estate. Washington Real Estate Board; Societies, Clubs and Organizations. D.C. Association of Realtors
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Bp - Washington E
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Building Congress
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Canoe Club SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Sycamore Island Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington City Society for the Promotion of Temperance
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Coalition for Clean Air
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Council of Agencies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Council of Church Women
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Council of Social Workers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Criminal Justice Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington D.C. Association of Realtors SEE ALSO Real Estate. Washington Real Estate Board
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Engineers' Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Ethical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington F - Washington H
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Fellowship
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Golf and Country Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Hearing Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Hearing Society. Newsletters
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Heart Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Housing Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Humane Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Humane Society. Newsletters
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington I - Washington M
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Interfaith Network
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Lawyers Committee for Civil Rights Under Law
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Lay Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Map Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Map Society. Newsletters
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Medical and Surgical Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Ministerial Union
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington N - Washington R
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Performing Arts Society (WPAS)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Playground Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Press Club SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. National Press Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Print Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Project for the Arts SEE Art. Washington Project for the Arts
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Radio Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Real Estate Brokers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Regional Alcohol Program
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Revels
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington S
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Society of Engineers
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Story League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington T - Washington Z
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Taxpayers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Trade Association Executives
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Urban League (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Water Color Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Yacht Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washington Youth Council
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Washingtonians
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wb - Wi
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wellesley Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. White House Correspondents Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. White House Historical Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. White House News Photographers Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. White Party of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wild Flower Preservation Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Woman's Welfare Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women in Cable
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's A - Women's Z
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Advertising Clubs
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Anthropological Society of America
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Army and Navy League
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Bar Association of D.C.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Christian Temperance Union (WCTU)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's City Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Club of Chevy Chase, Maryland, Inc.
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's District Golf Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's International League of Peace and Freedom, Washington Branch
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's Liberation
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's National Book Association
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's National Committee for Law Enforcement
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's National Democratic Club SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Metropolitan Women's Democratic Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Women's National Press Club (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Wonderful Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Woodrow Wilson International Center for Scholars
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. World Future Society
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Writers Conference
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Writers League of Washington
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. X - Y
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Ya - Yz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YMCA (by date)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YMCA. Anthony Bowen Branch (12th Street Branch)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YMCA. Historical Record of Washington YMCA - USO Club
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Youth Nation
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YWCA
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. YWCA. Phyllis Wheatley
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Za - Zz
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Zonta Club
- Society SEE Social Life
- Softball SEE Sports. Softball
- Solar Energy SEE ALSO Businesses, Individual. Solar Energy
- Soldiers and Sailors Temporary Home SEE Temporary Home for Soldiers and Sailor
- Soldiers' Home (by date)
- Somerset SEE Metropolitan District. Maryland. Somerset
- Songs SEE Music. Songs
- Sons and Daughters of the Year SEE Prizes. Sons and Daughter of the Year
- Sororities SEE Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Fraternities and Sororities
- Soul Music SEE Music. Soul
- South African Embassy Protest SEE Picketing, Protest, Demonstrations. South African Embassy, 1984
- Southeast SEE Residential Sections. Southeast
- Southeast Freeway SEE Streets. Southeast and Southwest Freeways
- Southeast House SEE Settlements. Southeast House
- Southeastern University SEE Colleges and Universities. Southeastern
- Southern Railroad SEE Railroads. Southern
- Southwest SEE Residential Sections. Southwest
- Southwest Freeway SEE Streets. Southeast and Southwest Freeways
- Southwest Farmers Market SEE Markets. Southwest Farmers Market
- Southwest House SEE Settlements. Southwest House
- Souvenir Shops SEE Business, Individual. Souvenir Shops
- Souvenirs
- So-V SEE Stores. So-V
- Spanish-American War
- Sparrows SEE Birds. Sparrows
- Special Days SEE Days. Special
- Special Months SEE Months. Special
- Special Olympics SEE Sports. Special Olympics
- Special Schools SEE Public Schools. Special
- Speech
- Speed SEE Traffic. Speed
- Spelling Contests (by date)
- Spies SEE ALSO Crime and Criminals. Specific Cases. Espionage
- Spiritualism ( includes Faith Healing)
- Spiritualist Churches SEE Churches. Spiritualist
- Sports (by date) SEE ALSO Public Schools. Sports; Colleges and Universities. Sports
- Sports. A-M
- Sports. Archery
- Sports. Automobiles Racing
- Sports. Baseball (by date)
- Sports. Baseball. Little League
- Sports. Basketball
- Sports. Basketball (by date)
- Sports. Basketball. Women's
- Sports. Bicycling SEE Bicycling
- Sports. Bowling (by date)
- Sports. Boxing (by date)
- Sports. Boxing. Legislation
- Sports. Coasting
- Sports. Croquet
- Sports. Darts
- Sports. Fencing
- Sports. Football (by date)
- Sports. Football. Federal (USFL)
- Sports. Football. Metro Buccaneers
- Sports. Football. Redskins
- Sports. Football. Redskins. Super Bowl XXII
- Sports. Fox Hunting
- Sports. Golf (by date) SEE ALSO Societies, Clubs and Organizations. Names of specific golf club
- Sports. Gunning SEE Sports. Shooting
- Sports. Gymnastics
- Sports. Hiking (by date)
- Sports. Hiking. Maps
- Sports. Hockey (by date)
- Sports. Ice Skating (by date)
- Sports. Jogging
- Sports. Jousting
- Sports. Judo
- Sports. Kayaking SEE ALSO Sports. Rowing
- Sports. Kickball
- Sports. Kite Flying
- Sports. Lacrosse
- Sports. Legislation SEE ALSO Sports. Boxing. Legislation
- Sports. Marathons SEE ALSO Sports. Running
- Sports. Martial Arts
- Sports. N-Z (by date)
- Sports. Olympic Bid
- Sports. Olympics
- Sports. Polo (by date)
- Sports. Roller Derby
- Sports. Roller Skating
- Sports. Rowing
- Sports. Rugby
- Sports. Running SEE ALSO Sports. Marathons
- Sports. Shooting
- Sports. Skateboarding
- Sports. Skiing (by date)
- Sports. Sledding SEE Sports. Coasting
- Sports. Soccer (by date)
- Sports. Softball (by date)
- Sports. Special Olympics
- Sports. Swimming (by date)
- Sports. Swimming. Beaches
- Sports. Swimming. Pools (by date)
- Sports. T-Ball
- Sports. Table Tennis
- Sports. Tennis (by date)
- Sports. Track (by date)
- Sports. Volleyball
- Sports. Wrestling (by date)
- Sports. Yoga
- Sports and Entertainment Commission, D.C.
- Spring Valley SEE Residential Sections. Spring Valley
- Springs
- St. Anne's Infant Asylum SEE Children's Homes. St. Anne's Infant Asylum
- St. Catherine's Residence for Business and Professional Women
- St. John's Child Development Center SEE Private Schools. St. John's Child Development Center
- St. John's Orphanage SEE Children's Homes. St. John's Orphanage
- St. Joseph's Home and School SEE Children's Homes. St. Joseph's Home and School
- St. Mary's Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. St. Mary's
- St. Patrick's Day SEE Days, Special. St. Patrick's Day
- St. Patrick's Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. St. Patrick's
- St. Peter's Cemetery SEE Cemeteries. St. Peter's
- St. Vincent's Home and School SEE Children's Homes. St. Vincent's Home and School
- Stables SEE Business, Individual. Stables and Livery Stables; Horses. Stables; White House. Stables
- Stadiums (by date)
- Stadiums. Capitol Center
- Stadiums. FedEx Field (Jack Kent Cooke Stadium)
- Stadiums. Griffith
- Stadiums. Legislation
- Stadiums. Proposed
- Stadiums. Riverside
- Stadiums. Robert F. Kennedy Memorial Stadium (by date)
- Stage Door Canteen SEE Theaters. Belasco
- Stagecoach
- Stamp, Seal and Stencil Manufacturing SEE Business, Individual. Stamp, Seal and Stencil Manufacturing
- Stamps
- Standards, Bureau of (now National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST))
- Stanton Park SEE Residential Sections. Stanton Park
- Starlings SEE Birds. Starlings
- Starplex SEE Armory
- State Department Buildings (by date)
- State Education Office
- State Health Planning and Development Agency (by date)
- State, War and Navy Building
- Statehood Movement SEE Politics and Government. Statehood Movement
- States' Buildings (proposed)
- Statistics
- Statistics. Area Labor Summary [Missing folder]
- Statistics. Comparative (by date)
- Statistics. Comparative. Pamphlets
- Statistics. Newspaper Clippings
- Statistics. Trends Magazine
- Statistics. Vital (by date)
- Statistics. Vital. Birth Registration
- Statuary Hall SEE Capitol. Statuary Hall
- Statues SEE Memorials. Statues
- Status of Women SEE Commission on the Status of Women
- Steuben Memorial SEE Memorials. Steuben, Baron von
- Stock Exchange (by date)
- Stonecarving and Quarrying SEE Business, Individual. Stonecarving and Quarrying
- Storage SEE Business, Individual. Storage
- Storefront Churches SEE Churches. Storefront
- Stores (by date)
- Stores. A - C
- Stores. A and P ( Atlantic and Pacific) SEE Stores. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. (A and P)
- Stores. Ayre and Taylor
- Stores. Barber and Ross
- Stores. Beckers
- Stores. Biggs Antique
- Stores. Blackistone
- Stores. Brentanos
- Stores. Chain
- Stores. Colony House
- Stores. Cooperative
- Stores. Crown Books
- Stores. Curtis Brothers [Missing folder]
- Stores. D-I (by date)
- Stores. District Grocery
- Stores. Doris Hat Stores
- Stores. Drug
- Stores. Drug. CVS
- Stores. Drug. Dart
- Stores. Drug. Drug Fair (by date)
- Stores. Drug. Fantles
- Stores. Drug. People's (by date)
- Stores. Fannie Mae Candy
- Stores. Federal Bake Shop
- Stores. Fresh Fields
- Stores. Galt and Bros.
- Stores. Garfinckel's (by date) (ceased 1990)
- Stores. Garrison's
- Stores. Gartenhaus
- Stores. Georgetown
- Stores. Giant (by date)
- Stores. Ginns
- Stores. Golden Rule Supermarket
- Stores. Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. (A and P)